This is my wedding.
I don't need a hall
pass to invite my friends.
This is the Holy Cathedral,
a place even King Byas rarely enters.
And you bring
two filthy miners here?
You are trying to
humiliate me on purpose!
When we got engaged,
your father was nothing but a miner himself.
What, you’ve forgotten where you came from?
You…
I chose you
because I saw something real and pure in you.
I defied my father
and got engaged anyway.
But vanity consumed you.
Are you saying
our family only rose
because of your so-called protection?
Severin,
have you lost your goddamn mind?
A disowned failure standing here badmouthing
the most desired woman in Emeraldstone?
I can’t stand this trash for one more second.
Redmond, where is your father?
They should be here any moment.
I sent someone to check.
Make way for Count Arthur Carter!
Forgive my late arrival.
I haven’t been well today.